hello guys my answers here and welcome
to my channel in today's video guys if
Apogee purpose I know how fast and
convenient it is to get insured online
through FWD insurance
just a quick background about FWD
insurance guys FWD Life Insurance
Corporation is the first life insurance
company licensed by the Insurance
Commission of the Philippines under the
new insurance code so they are 100%
legit so nothing to worry and they span
across Asia Marin Cilic Hong Kong Macau
Thailand and the Philippines and be me
more so if you wanna know more about FWD
insurance you can visit their website
PayPal wlwt.com that ph so today guys i
am going to get my insurance at FWD
insurance emergency land first step of
online products which is the can do K a
and D you you can do I will be doing a
screen recording and illa llah guy could
be thrown aside para Mikasa by kayo and
para Makita you how easy it is to get
insured through FWD insurance through
the shaft that FWD that come that pH you
can buy your insurance online no medical
no paperwork Marin is an exciting part
earn rewards and you can manage
everything in the app and if a tri
coinsurance is the can do plan Neela can
do covers you so you can do everything
you want in life with no hesitations so
cinnamon among unique astana at peace
your mind move because you are insured
so nothing to worry FWD insurance got
your back
so under the condo plan Marin Pat low
plans now when I move back te and so
first is the can mend so can man is a
protection against 42 critical illnesses
no medical test six months and Lee
telemedicine reward you got covered up
to 100,000 pesos guys and it
only 1799 per year so all of these can
do nah
plants is only 1799 per year it's
payable per year so I you an can mend
and then Marin Dean can live essential
funds for your family and one year only
medical consults rewards you've got a
live coverage of up to two hundred
thousand pesos to get to know more about
the plan you can visit their website at
triple w dot shop that FWD that calmed
at ph p-- aramas my scrutinize new home
under your plan now best new suits a new
and then the third plan is can't guard
so it is a accident and terrorism
coverage you are covered up to five
hundred thousand pesos let's be
practical it's it's a good deal nadi bad
guys can guard payout for accidents or
terror attacks worldwide coverage and
one year global emergency services
reward so today like I said who happen
an insurance for myself sat at low nappa
PPE and I will be choosing can live I
will be showing to you guys how to
purchase online at all can live so life
insurance covered up to two hundred
thousand pesos Union and it's only one
thousand seven hundred ninety nine per
year so okay let's buy now so after that
now pick you by now you have to enter
your details so fill up fill up alarm
so this is your name your birthday and
contact information your present address
additional information your citizenship
Filipino of course then proof of
identity so you have to upload a clear
photo of your ID so I will be uploading
a valid ID you driver's license go see
your numerical dito and then your
options if you don't pay your premiums
and declaration so you have to declare I
have never had not receive medical so
you have to read all the declarations
carefully huh so but beside in pull up
and I'll get back to you all right
so I agree and then at the bottom so you
will be paying a premium of 1799 per
year and the payment payment mode is
annual covered up to age 55 sum assured
two hundred thousand then the benefit
coverage is that due to any costs so
it's a life insurance and then it's
lucious marital ago exclusion you will
get to know more about the exclusions
when you visit their website so you
be signal first to know more about it so
let's click continue but it
information so summary you have to check
the summary before nothing is submit so
once time a check now confirm and pay
via dragon pay you can pay guys using
your credit card or debit card so let's
fill out so let's fill out the billing
information so I will be paying you see
my credit card enough so click Next
input then review your order this review
total amount is or 1780 pay just some
sort of validation sub card Maggie
nameko and then just a few minutes
I am ensure no need to go dance office
nila to fill up fill out all the forms
or the papers
what up through online long Pellegrin
just using your mobile I'm just using my
mobile phone to get my insurance so I
own a Biba amazing alright so guys gonna
Lanka easy so just stop in your phone
and then now I'm insured Vibha easy
super easy you CK audio so I am
encouraging you guys to get your to get
insured and might as well try the FWD
insurance can do plans so they're very
easy to purchase easy to buy you just do
it online over your phone tap tap tap
thank the box you're insured so I um
thank you so much guys for watching if
you like this video please give it a
thumbs up and might as well subscribe
that into channel go and leave some
mence down below because salam against
effect on now and i hope to see you guys
on my next video have a great day
everyone
bye
[Music]